//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"How many club did Christian Vieri play for?",
        answer: "13",
        options:[
            "14",
            "8",
            "12",
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Zinedine Zidane won two serie A title with which team",
        answer: "Juventus",
        options:[
            "Inter Milan",
            "A C Milan",
            "Juventus",
            "AS Roma"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Which English city was the founder of Italian club AC Milan from?",
        answer: "Nottingham",
        options:[
            "London",
            "Leicester",
            "Bristol",
            "Nottingham"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"In which year did AC Milan won their first Serie A title?",
        answer: "1901",
        options:[
            "1901",
            "1899",
            "1911",
            "1903"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Which stricker was the three times top scorer in the 90s, when he played for Lazio?",
        answer: "Giuseppe Signori",
        options:[
            "Alen Boksic",
            "Gianluca Vialli",
            "Oliver Bierhoff",
            "Giuseppe Signori"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"which is the foundation of Juventus?(old Lady)",
        answer: "1897",
        options:[
            "1905",
            "1897",
            "1901",
            "1900"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"In which city is Juventus Based?",
        answer: "Turin",
        options:[
            "Turin",
            "Rome",
            "Milano",
            "Firenze"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Which club won the most Serie A?",
        answer: "Juventus",
        options:[
            "Ac Milan",
            "Juventus",
            "Genoa cfc",
            "Inter Milan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"Which player has scored the most number of goals in the serie A history?",
        answer: "Silvio Piola",
        options:[
            "Francesco Totti",
            "Gunnar Nordahl",
            "Silivio Piola",
            "Giuseppe"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Which goalkeeper has the most number of clean sheet in Serie A history?",
        answer: "Gianluigi Buffon",
        options:[
            "Dino Zoff",
            "Giovanni Galli",
            "Samir Handanovic",
            "Gianluigi Buffon"
        ]
    },
];